# **Thor Lindberg**

## Reykjavík, Iceland

Email thor@lindberg.is

Website lindberg.is

Courses lindberg.is/certificates

GitHub github.com/thorlindberg

LinkedIn linkedin.com/in/thorlindberg

#### **Profile**

M.Sc. Design with a background in the intersection between medical science and information technology. With this interdisciplinary perspective I act as a bridge between clients, design and development teams. This is evident from my experience in consulting, where I was involved in projects from leading initial analysis to authoring design specification to collaborating with developer on planning and implementing in code.

I invest my spare time in writing software, supplementing my education with courses, and traveling in the U.S. to network with others in tech.

#### **Education**

IT University of Copenhagen, 2022

### **Master of Science in Digital Design**

Thesis: Type-Extensible Objection Notation (TXON)

Explorative design for typed JSON objects.

# Relevant courses:

 React Native mobile development with Expo. Advanced Design Processes. UX Design.

Copenhagen University, 2020

## **Bachelor of Science in Health Informatics**

Thesis: Tools for caretakers of stroke victims

 Qualitative analysis to determine low-cost digital solutions for caretakers of stroke victims.

## Relevant courses:

 Statistics. Mathematical Modelling. Programming for Biosciences. IT Security. Medical Image Analysis. Interaction Design.

# Skills

Language Fluent in English and Danish

Figma Components, variants, flows, auto layout

Software React, JSX, TypeScript, Swift, Git, Azure

Analysis Python, NumPy, Pandas, Matplotlib

Data Excel, Visual Basic for Applications

Writing LaTeX, Markdown, Microsoft Word

# **Experience**

Netcompany, 08/2022 - 12/2023

#### **IT Consultant**

- Responsible for leading project analysis with clients and authoring feature specification and design documentation for digital solutions.
- · Responsible for client contact, mediating meetings, status reporting.
- Provided clients an analysis of their digital infrastructure and strategies for digital transformation through decoupling of dependencies.
- · Contributed to new source code for Java-based backend.
- · Contributed to source code for a React Native application.

National Special Crime Unit, 10/2021 - 07/2022

#### **IT-Administrative Student**

- · Managed users of webportal and provided direct support.
- · Contributed to document processing architecture.
- · Authored documentation and website content.

IT University of Copenhagen, 08/2021 - 06/2022

# **Teaching Assistant**

- Assisted with teaching UX Design specialization by planning and conducting course material for post-lecture activities and exercises.
- Assisted students with their assignments for courses in UX Design, Experimental Design, Python, and Javascript with MQTT.

Domino's Pizza, 08/2021 - 01/2022

#### **Shift Leader**

- Responsible for managing the store, closing the store, registering inventory, and delegating work to bakers and delivery drivers.
- · Primary pizza baker during rush hours.

# **Professional certificates**

Meta, Not yet complete

# **Front-End Developer**

Courses: JavaScript. Version control. HTML and CSS. Advanced React with components, hooks, APIs, and testing. UX/UI design.

University of California in San Diego, Not yet complete

## **Data Structures and Algorithms**

Courses: Test-driven algorithm design. Dynamic programming. Advanced algorithms and data structures. Pattern matching.

MúltíKúltí, Not yet complete

# Icelandic 1 (A1.1)

"A beginner course to teach beginner level vocabulary and grammar and is therefore aimed at people who are complete beginners in Icelandic."

# **Published**

#### Áfangastaður - Explore Iceland

iPhone application on Apple App Store (apps.apple.com/app/id6466740299)